rockto.com 2012-05-23

# ROCKTO - Privacy Policy

ROCKTO ( Rockto, us, we ) is developed for helping people to share any rocking highlight everyday. We really concern about your personal information and take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting ROCKTO website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers ROCKTO's treatment of personal information that we gathers when you are on the ROCKTO website and when you use ROCKTO services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that ROCKTO does not own or control, or to individuals that ROCKTO does not employ or manage.

#### Information we collect are:

  1. When you register for ROCKTO, we will collect your email address and your full name.
  2. When you personalize your ROCKTO Profile, we will collect any information you provide, such as any other optional information about you, your lifestyle, and your interests.
  3. When you connect your ROCKTO to your other Social Media website, we just collect your email address that used to that Social Media website account. We don't and won't access any personal information in that Social Media website account.
  4. When you contact us by sending us an e-mail, we will collect your e-mail address and any information contained in the e-mail you send us.
  5. The ROCKTO Profile that you create when you register for our ROCKTO Services just contains email address as Personal Information. All the information in your ROCKTO Profile, including Personal Information, will be public information and any Rockers will be able to view it. Your username and general physical location will always be publicly displayed.

#### If you are a regular visitor to our site:

  1. ROCKTO's servers automatically record information when you visit our website, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request.
  2. ROCKTO uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use ROCKTO in order to improve the quality of our services.
  3. We track all searches in our system..
  4. We keep your IP address on file.
  5. We do not, and could not, cross-reference your searches with your IP address.
  6. What does this mean? All of your searches in our system are 100% anonymous. We are never able to connect a search with a specific person.

#### If you sign up for a user account, and share any highlight from your account:

  1. ROCKTO collects personal information when you register for a ROCKTO user account or otherwise voluntarily provide such information.
  2. We keep your email address on file.
  3. We do not share your email address with anyone.
  4. We do not contact you via your email address unless you have requested that we contact you.
  5. We keep your password on an encrypted file that we do not have the ability to read.
  6. We do not cross-reference your email address with our search logs.
  7. What does this mean? Although your activity in sharing highlights is tracked and tied to your IP address, as well as your email address if you are logged into your ROCKTO user account, all of your searches still remain 100% anonymous.

#### Information Collected Via Technology

An “Internet protocol address” or “IP Address” is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP Address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP Address probably varies from session to session. We track IP Addresses solely in conjunction with session cookies to analyze our web page flow.

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing a website. Cookies can identify you as a unique user of the Website. Upon your first use of the Toolbar, ROCKTO sends a Cookie to your computer. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on the Website. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of the Website may not work properly.

#### Use of Information

In general, Personal Information you submit to us is used by us either to sign you up for our community, to respond to requests that you make, to provide you with the Services, to improve our community and Services and to better tailor the features, performance and support of the Services and to offer you additional information, opportunities, and functionality. We may also use your email address to provide you with our notification from RobotRock.

Information you provide, with the exception of your email address, will also be displayed on your profile page which is viewable by other users of ROCKTO. These publicly displayed information just contains your username and full name in ROCKTO

If we delete your account at your request, we will delete all Personal Information from the account, but we retain the right to maintain non-personally identifiable information about the account (e.g. date created, date terminated, total post, etc.). Also, if we terminate your account as allowed under the Terms of Service, we may choose to maintain all data collected from your use of the ROCKTO Services, including Personal Information.

#### Other Sites

Our provision of links or access to other websites or locations is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other websites or location or its contents. The sites that linking from ROCKTO are entirely out of our control. As such, ROCKTO takes no responsibility for them, or their content. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Links to other websites or locations may also be posted by other ROCKTO Members within the ROCKTO community. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites.

#### Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit ROCKTO website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of country law. ROCKTO have rights to move every data to the third party that we believe to keep all assets and information.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, ROCKTO may change its privacy policy from time to time, and in ROCKTO sole discretion. ROCKTO encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its privacy policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

#### Effective Date of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 8 , 2010 and last updated October 8 , 2010.
